cartoonhd.website 2016-10-11

# Cartoon HD - Watch TV Shows Online Free | Watch Movies Online Free

### Cartoon HD Privacy Policy

###### This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you at www.cartoonhd.mobi (the "Website") and Cartoon HD applications and how we use this information.

###### **Collection of your Cartoon HD Information**

###### Your "Cartoon HD information" includes relevant technical information gathered or received while you use Cartoon HD. This technical information that may be collected or received includes: the type of browser you are using (e.g., Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, Safari), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), your CPU type, the manner in which you connect to the internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); Internet protocol address; pertinent Applications Installed; information about the version of service from an affiliate that you used prior to registering with the service; certain information about your geographic location; and the domain name of your Internet service provider.

###### You may not be required to register for a "Cartoon HD account" for certain Services; however, there are some optional services available (for example, saving a video list) that require an "account". Registration functionality for Cartoon HD is provided by the Cartoon HD Network. If you choose to "Register an Account", you will need to register with and provide information to Cartoon HD. After registering you will obtain a Screen Name, or possibly other credential, issued by Cartoon HD (collectively, "Screen Name") in order to access and use these optional services. Your Screen Name and associated services account will then be subject to the Cartoon HD Terms of Service Agreement and Privacy Policies indicated in the registration process and available to view at any time on www.cartoonhd.mobi.

###### **How Your Cartoon HD information is Used**

###### Your Cartoon HD information is used

######  •to operate and improve the websites, services and offerings available through Cartoon HD;   
•to personalize the content provided to you;   
•to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services;   
•to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;   
•to conduct research about your use of Cartoon HD; and   
•to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

###### Your Cartoon HD information will not be shared with third parties unless it is necessary to fulfill a request, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your Cartoon HD information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your Cartoon HD information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of Cartoon HD users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.

###### If you use our communications tools to disclose information about yourself publicly (for example, by making your screen name and/or video lists publicly available), other online users may obtain access to any information you provide. The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as a Cartoon HD user, may be accessed and disclosed in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); in other circumstances in which we believe Cartoon HD is being used in the commission of a crime; when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person; or when necessary either to protect our rights or property or the rights or property of our affiliated providers, or for us to render the service you have requested. We may use agents and contractors in order to help operate the service. If such agents and contractors have access to your Cartoon HD information, they are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Cartoon HD.

###### In the event that ownership of us or the Cartoon HD service was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your Cartoon HD information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your Cartoon HD information, we will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.

###### **Your Choices About Your Information**

###### If you want to change your account information (for example, your Screen Name) you will need to log onto Cartoon HD and access your account through the forum. Your access to your account information and choice will be governed by the Cartoon HD policies.

###### **Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies**

###### Cookies are text files that are placed in your computer's browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as a Cartoon HD user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browser's settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you will not be able to take advantage of certain Cartoon HD offerings.

###### We may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in combination with your Cartoon HD information to enhance and personalize your experience on Cartoon HD, including to operate and improve offerings through Cartoon HD; to help authenticate you when you use Cartoon HD; to remember your preferences; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of Cartoon HD offerings and advertisements; and, to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through Cartoon HD.

###### Cartoon HD and its advertisers may use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on Cartoon HD. These advertising networks may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. Any choices that you have about these technologies will be presented here in the event we utilize the services of any advertising network provider. Therefore, you are encouraged to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks.

###### Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.tv/privacy/ads/). (Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

###### We may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit http://networkadvertising.org/. 

###### **Security**

###### We have established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your Cartoon HD information, but cannot guarantee that this information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers).

###### Cartoon HD gives you a personal, worldwide, royalty-free, non-assignable and non-exclusive license to use the software provided to you by Cartoon HD as part of the Services. This license is for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the Services as provided by Cartoon HD, in the manner permitted by these terms. You may not copy, modify, distribute, sell, or lease any part of our Services or included software, nor may you reverse engineer or attempt to extract the source code of that software, unless laws prohibit those restrictions or you have our written permission.

###### **Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

###### We will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging your user account page

###### **How to Contact Us**

###### If you have any questions or concerns about Cartoon HD's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at info@cartoonhd.mobi.

###### **Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information**

###### We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to Cartoon HD's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from Cartoon HD, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.

###### Last Updated: January 27, 2015
